

#### **Tư Pham Minh**

Machine Learning Engineer at Vingroup Big Data Institute

Connect

**♠** Message

More...



Try Premium Free for 1 Month



Connect

**♠** Message

• • •

Tư Pham Minh · 3rd

Machine Learning Engineer at Vingroup Big Data Institute Hanoi Capital Region · 293 connections · **Contact info** 



**Vingroup Big Data Institute** 



Hanoi University of Science and Technology

People and pages related to Tu

See all



>



**TED Conferences** 

Page • Media Production 20,322,045 followers

#### **Follow**



Page • Research 66,892 followers

#### **Follow**



#### **European Research Council**

Page • Research 86,724 followers

**Follow** 

### About

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Python (Programming Language), Computer Vision, Image Processing, C (Programming Language), and Machine Learning. Strong engineering professional with a Engineer's degree focused in Computer Scie

... see more

## Activity

293 followers

Posts Tu created, shared, or commented on in the last 90 days are displayed here.

See all activity

## Experience

#### **Machine Learning Engineer**

/ingroup Big Data Institute · Full-time Oct 2020 – Present

VINBIGDATA. 7 mos

#### Al Developer at Kaopiz Software Co.,Ltd

Kaopiz Software Co.,Ltd · Full-time (kaopiz Jul 2018 – Oct 2020 · 2 yrs 4 mos

#### Education

#### **Hanoi University of Science and Technology**



Engineer's degree, Computer Science 2015 – 2020

#### Licenses & certifications

#### **Convolutional Neural Networks**

Coursera ssued Sep 2020 · No Expiration Date Credential ID 4QBT4Z2W32UM

See credential

## Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter tuning, Regularization and Optimization

coursera ssued Sep 2020 · No Expiration Date redential ID A4G9RV6QS6MP

See credential

#### Introduction to TensorFlow for Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning, and Deep Learning

coursera ssued Sep 2020 · No Expiration Date credential ID 9X38Q8CQAN8U

See credential

Show more 🗸

# **Computer Vision Python Developer** No endorsements yet Ź LinkedIn Skill Assessment badge C (Programming Language) Industry Knowledge **Machine Learning Image Processing** Tools & Technologies JavaScript Python (Programming Language) Show less ^ Interests **VNEXT HOLDINGS** ,288 followers

1,288 follower

Vingroup Big Data Institute

1,684 followers



Kaopiz Software Co.,Ltd

161 followers

(**k**aopiz



18,104 followers

## People also viewed



Alexey Golunov •3rd

Lead Machine Learning Engineer at Incode Technologies

Connect



An Tran Cong Viet •3rd

NLP Engineering Intern at Vingroup Big Data Institute - VinBDI

Connect



Thanh Nguyen Kim •3rd

Developer Embedded software at Global CyberSoft JSC

Connect



**Ai Nguyen •**3rd

Data Scientist | Machine Learning Engineer

Connect



**Lê Hùng •**3rd

Al Researcher at Cinnamon Al

Connect

**∨**Show more

## People you may know



BE BA (My Nguyen)

Recruitment Specialist cum Admin at Milensea Retail

Connect



Le Nhat Huy

President at UTE Logistics and Supply Chain Club

Connect



Khánh Linh Đỗ

Human Resources Assistant at Hachinet Software

Connect



Nguyen Dinh Dat

Frontend Angular Developer

Nhi Duong	
Student at Ton Duc Thang University	
Connect	
	→Show more
n LEARNING	
Add new skills with these courses	
introduction to Deep Learning with OpenCV	
18,355 viewers	
Google Cloud Platform for Machine Learning Essential	aining
14,183 viewers	
Building Recommender Systems with Machine Learning	and Al
31,975 viewers	
3,513 1.616.6	Show more on LinkedIn Learning

Connect

About

Accessibility	
Falent Solutions	
Community Guidelines	
Careers	
Marketing Solutions	
Privacy & Terms ✓	
Ad Choices	
Advertising	
Sales Solutions	
Mobile Control of the	
Small Business	
Safety Center	
Questions?  Visit our Help Center.	
Manage your account and privacy Go to your Settings.	
Select Language	
(Arabic) العربية	
inkedIn Corporation © 2021	
	<b>B</b>
	•••

